(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
You're interested in Plot 73 too
I'm interested in the new Development zone
It's good for young people to have guts
But it depends on who you're up against
In business, winner takes all
It's all about financial strength
Then let's wait and see
Plot 73
Prosperity Group must win it
The live bidding is already at 8 billion
Young Master Sheng is awaiting your orders
Who placed the bid?
The Long family, Zhang Xiaobei
Match it
Yes
Father, it's already up to 10 billion
Match it
Okay, Father
Wait, don't hang up
I want updates immediately
11 billion
11.5 billion
12 billion
Father
This price far exceeds
its profit value
I want Plot 73
Chairman Sheng, congrats on becoming the new land king
What?
A financial group from Singapore
decided to invest 20 billion in the West District
to build a top-tier deep-water port in the country
If the deep-water port
is built in the West District
then the East District's chances of being the Development zone
will be very small
What about the West District?
Did anyone buy it?
This afternoon
Plot 32 in the West District
was sold for 6.2 billion
Who bought it?
All we know is he's a rich businessman from Shanxi
After weighing multiple factors
we've decided
in Jinghai City's West District
to establish a new Development zone
and focus on developing it
around the West deep-water port
into a Port City
They think
our 12 billion cost basis is too high
the market generally lacks confidence in our profitability
and development will be hard to push forward
Prosperity Group shares
Buy as much as you can
Someone's buying up large amounts of
Prosperity Group shares
but we don't know who it is yet
Sheng Yuanzhou. He must be behind this
I'm gonna kill him
Zhang Xiaobei
Explain this to me
Where did you get it?
Someone mailed it to the Newspaper office where I work
Spit it out!
Did you poison Master Long?
How could I?
Master Long
You're cured of the poison?
I was never poisoned
I checked it
Only the surface was laced with poison
They're trying to use you to get rid of me
and then pin it on you
Perfect, then
We'll beat them at their own game
This is a fake Long Family Inkstone
and the Baochi Motors files
I'm counting on you for everything
Don't worry
I've never misjudged anyone
Sorry
For making you worry
To fool that old fox Sheng Shizhong
we have to fool everyone
I get it
Hot, hot, hot!
Coming through, coming through! Make way!
Lisa
Big Sis Si Qi, you're here
So that day
you were putting on an act too
Otherwise
how could we get Sheng Shizhong to spare no expense?
This Malatang place is really good
Big Sis Si Qi, here
Chopsticks
I won't join you
I have things to do
You guys go ahead
Go on back
Ride safe, okay?
Don't worry
I've gotten the hang of it now
I'm off
I really underestimated him
He actually picked up a lot of skills from the Long family
The public announcement is out
HA Capital has already acquired
over five percent of Prosperity Group's shares
From what I know
it's the same person who bought the plot in the West District
Looks like they're coming for me
Go look into it
You must find this person
No matter what it takes
I want to meet him myself
I found him
He really likes fishing
He often goes to Yingzhou Fishing Ground
Yingzhou Fishing Ground
It's you
Long time no see
No way
You're just a driver
How could you have that much money?
Where there's a will, there's a way
After all, I'm the real Sheng Shizhong
Bullshit!
I'm the real Sheng Shizhong
I am!
It doesn't matter anymore
Bai Zimei is gone
Whether I'm Sheng Shizhong or not
means nothing to me
Right now, for me
the only thing that matters
is making sure you're left with nothing again
to avenge Zimei
Impossible
How could you do that?
I won't let you make a comeback
I won't let you!
So, how was I? Did I look convincing?
Judging by his reaction,
he definitely bought it.
It's time to close the net.
It's not this guy.
His name is Hu Jin.
Hu Jin.
How could he know he's Sheng Shizhong?
Did he use my Key of Fate?
No way.
He doesn't even know the Key of Fate exists.
Impossible.
Unless...
Zhang Xiaobei.
Welcome.
What room are those two from earlier in?
I'm sorry.
We can't share other guests' information.
You don't recognize me?
Sorry, Mr. Sheng.
Those two from earlier are in Room 608.
Fa...
Where are they?
Father.
Get out here!
Father, let me explain!
Get the hell away from me!